Atmospheric Sciences and Research Center; Records ua450
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1961-1992; 3; 5.5 cubic ft.
  - Possibilities for Atmospheric Aerosol Formation involving NH3- C.S. Kiang, D. Stauffer, and V.A. Mohnen, 1973 July (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 315)
  - Heteromolecular Condensation Theory Applied to Particle Growth- D. Stauffer, V.A. Mohnen, and C.S. Kiang, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 316)
  - A Portable Aerosol Detector of High Sensitivity- A. Hogan and W. Winters, 1974 September (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 317)
  - Development of an Ultra High Frequency Radiolocation System for Studying Birds- F.C. Craighead Jr., Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 319)
  - Introduction to the Atmosphere Aerosol System, 1973 August 23 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 322)
  - ASPECTS, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 324)
  - Electrostatic uses in Home & Industry- D.L. McClenahan, 1974 February (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 325)
  - Atmospheric Particulates- Final Report- J.E. Jiusto, G.G. Lala, R.A. Glassbrook, T.D. Lee & E. Mandel, 1974 January (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 326)
  - Ionometric Counter- V.A. Mohnen, 1969 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 328)
  - Handling Hot Water, With a Payoff-R.Stewart & S.P. Mathur, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 331)
  - Research Material as a Classroom Resource- T.W. Norton, 1974 May (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 332)
  - Progress Toward Tracking Migrating Raptors by Satellite- F.C. Craighead Jr. & T.C. Dunstan, 1976 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 333)
  - The Mirco-Physics of the Atmosphere- R.J. Cheng, 1971 January 14 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 334)
  - The Effect of Ozone on Lead and Silver Iodide- V.J. Schaefer, 1974 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 337)
  - Weather Modification Outlook- 1985 Production- J.E. Juisto, 1974 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 338)
  - High Concentration Of Condensation Nuclei in the Lower Stratosphere- V.J. Schaefer, 1973 September (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 339)
  - Using Fresh Approaches, Science is Helping Power to be a Good Neighbor- R. Stewart, 1974 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 340)
  - ASRC Report 1973-1974 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 341)
  - Observation, Serendipity, and Climate Change- V.J. Shaefer, 1974 September (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 343)
  - A Population Analysis of the Yellowstone Grizzly Bears- J.J. Craighead, J.R. Varney, and F.C. Craighead Jr., 1974 September (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 344)
  - A Mobile Tracing Technique Utilizing a Meteorology Hert Lithium Areosol- A.W. Hogan & T.A. Rich, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 345)
  - Cloud Physics Review- Laboratory & Field Observations (1970-1974)- J.E. Juisto (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 346)
  - Radiotelemetry Research on Large Western Mammals in Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1967- F.C. Craighead Jr. & J.J. Craighead, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 347)
  - A Numerical Model of Radiation Fog- G.G. Lala, E. Mendel, and J.E. Jiusto, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 348)
  - Remarks on Visibility in Fog- J.E. Juisto, 1974 August (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 349)
  - Urban Influences on Diural Concentrations of Cloud Condensation Nuclei- J.E. Juisto & T.D. Lee, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 350)
  - Diural Variations in Cloud Condensation Nuclei- T.D. Lee & J.E. Jiusto, 1974 December 20 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 351)
  - Some Physical Relationships of Fine Particle Smoke- V.J. Schaefer, 1973 March (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 352)
  - Soalr Energy For New York State- Solar Energy Experiments for Secondary School Students 1 of 2, 1975 February (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 353)
  - Solar Energy For New York State- Solar Energy Experiments for Secondary School Students 2 of 2, 1975 February (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 353)
  - Soalr Energy for New York State: Solar Attenuation Model for an Urban Area- Albany, New York, 1975 February (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 354)
  - Solar Energy for New York State: Solar Energy Atlas for New York State, 1975 March (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 355)
  - Solar Energy for New York State: Solar Supplements for Chemistry Courses, 1975 March (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 356)
  - Solar Energy for New York State: Cloud Cover Deduced from Satellite Observations, 1975 March (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 358)
  - Gas to Particle Conversion of Sulfur Dioxide Reaction Products at Low Relative Humidities- V.H. Mohne, 1975 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 363)
  - The Inadvertentert Modification of the atmosphere by Air Pollution -V.J. Schaefer, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 364)
  - Final Report on the Second Inadvertent Weather Modification Workshop- V.J. Schaefer, E. McLaren, and D. Blanchard, 1974 October (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 366)
  - July Currents Near the South Shore of Lake Ontario- J.T. Scott & D.R. Landsberg, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 367)
  - Collection of Drifting Snow by a Traek- Roughended Surface- A.W. Hogen, 1975 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 368)
  - Aerosol Observations over the Ice Caps- A.W. Hogan & D. Nelson, 1975 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 370)
  - Minimum Energy Solar Heated Demonstration Project- D. L. McClenahan, 1975 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 371)
  - Antartic Aerosols- A.W. Hogan, 1975 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 372)
  - Aerosol Technology II: Changes on Aerols- T.A.Rich, 1975 May (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 373)
  - Project Sunshine- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 374)
  - Conference Summery: General Statement by Participents of the Second Inadvertent Weather Modification Workshop- D.C. Blanchard & V.A. Mohnen, 1975 August (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 376)
  - More Heat from Your Fireplace- V.J. Schaefer, 1975 November (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 377)
  - Some Aspects of Size Measurements in Aerosols- T.A. Rich, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 378)
  - A Trip on the Colorado through the Grand Canyon- V.J. Schaefer, 1975 October 8 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 379)
  - SO2 Oxidation Rate In Plumes from Oil Fired Power Plants- A Laboratory Study, 1976 February (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 380)
  - Investigating Freely Suspended Water- Drop Interactions With High-Speed Photography- J.D. Spengler & N.R. Gokhale, 1971 July (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 381)
  - Dew & Fog Relationships as Affected by Ambient Humidity & Soil Moisture Conditions- K.E. Pickering, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 382)
  - A Comparison of the Langer, Rosen, Nolan-Pollak, and SANDS Condensation Nucleus Counters- R.D. Cadle, G, Langer, J.B. Haberl, A. Hogan, J.M. Rosen, W. A. Sedlacek, J. Wegrzyn, 1975 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 384)
  - Aerosols of the Trade Wind Region- A.W. Hogan, 1976 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 385)
  - Thermal Discharge: An Alternate Energy Source- R.Stewart, 1975 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 386)
  - Climate, Air Pollution, and Agriculture- A.R. Breisch, R, Stewart & J. Kadlecek, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 390)
  - Proposed Northeastern New York Chapter of the American Section of the International Solar Energy Society: Conference Proceding, 1976 February (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 391)
  - Project Dustorm Report: Ozone Measurements & Meterological Analysis of Tropopause Folding- E.F. Danielsen & V.A. Mohnen, 1976 May (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 394)
  - Measurements of Background Hydrocarbons In Remote Areas- L.Ruther, R. Whitby, V.A. Mohnen, and P. Roffey, 1976 May (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 395)
  - Characterization of Particulates from Power Plants- R.J. Cheng, V.A. Mohnen, T.T. Shen, M. Current, and J.D. Hudson, 1976 August (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 398)
  - Life or Death for Teton Canyon- F.G. Craighead Jr., Undated (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 399)
  - Papers & Procedings from the Third International Conference on Bears, Their Biology and Management, 1974 June (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 400)
  - Assessment of Ion-Induced Stratospheric Aerosol Formation- V.A. Mohnen & C.S. King, 1976 April (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 402)
  - Solar Energy for New York State: Minimum Energy Buildingthe first Winter's Operation- D.L. McClenahen & H.P. Misuriello, 1976 December (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 405)
  - The Air Quality Patterns of Aerosols on the Global Scale Part III- V.S. Schaefer, 1976 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 406)
  - Production of Air Bubbles of a Specified Size- D.C. Blanchard & L.D. Syzdek, 1977 (Box 3 (3-Publications), Folder 411)
  - ASRC Reports 1975-1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 412)
  - Atomospheric Ion Molecule Interactions Involving Chlorofluorocarbons- J.A. Kadlecek, V.A. Mohnen, and & J.Del Santo, 1977 January 31 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 414)
  - Energy Conservation Via Solar Energy Application to Multi-Family and Commerical Structures- V.A. Mohnen & R. Stewart, 1976 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 417)
  - Solar-Climate Zones and Respective Design Year Data for New York Sate- B.H. Bailey, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 418)
  - Solar Energy Atlas for New York State: Part II- B.H. Bailey, J. Healey, and R. Stewart, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 419)
  - An Energy, Engineering & Economic Analysis of Heating & Cooling Systems for Multi-Family Structures- W.S. Fleming, T. Bender, T. Jagusztyn, P. Parkment, and D.Sweetser, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 420)
  - Energy Conservation+ Via Solar Energy Application to Multi-Family and Commerical Structures- E.R. Allen & E.G. Malawer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 422)
  - Economic Analysis of Energy Conservation Methods- B. Murphy, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 423)
  - Measurements of PH in Cloud Water & Precipitation at Whiteface Mountain in the Northeastern Adirondacks of New York State- R.E. Falconer & R.E. Farrell, 1977 February (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 425)
  - Cloud Physics Survey Articles and Review- J. Jiusto, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 426)
  - Characterization of Differences between Oil-Fired & Coal- Fired Power Plant Emission- T.T. Shen, V.A. Mohnen, M.Current & J.B. Hudsun, 1977 May 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 427)
  - New York State Solar Network- R.Stewart, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 428)
  - Ball Lightning- B.H. Bailey, 1977 June (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 431)
  - Heating Degree-Days, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 432)
  - The Formation of Small Sparks- E. Barreto, H. Vurenka, S.I. Reynolds, 1977 November (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 433)
  - Catalyst Plugging in Thruway Police Vechicles- G.P. Wotzak, N.P. Kolak, R.E. Gibbs, and R.J. Cheng, 1977 June (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 434)
  - Snow Crystal Observations in Summer Season at Amundsen- Scott South Pole Station, Antartica- K.Kikuchi & A.W. Hogan, 1976 December (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 435)
  - Third International Conference on Bears- Their Biology and Management, 1974 June (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 437)
  - Measurement of Maximum Electric Field Intensities Over Water During Thunderstorms- R.B. Toland & B. Vonnegut, 1977 January (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 438)
  - Report on Workshop Goals, Program, Instruments, Observations, and Preliminary Analysis, 1971 May (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 439)
  - Contribution to the Problem of the Collection Efficiency of the Falling Ice Cystal- J. Podzimek, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 440)
  - Lightning Photography- R.E. Orville, 1971 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 444)
  - Comments on "Precipitation Process Revealed by Cosmogenic Radionuclide Scavenging"- R.E. Oriville, 1972 May (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 445)
  - Close Lightning- R.E. Oriville, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 446)
  - Lightning-R.E. Oriville, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 447)
  - The Laboratory Study of the Freezing of Supercold Fog Droplets- J.Podzimek, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 448)
  - Electrostatic Collection of Jet & Film Drops- D.C. Blanchard & L.D. Sydek, 1975 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 449)
  - Ions, Basic Research: Formation, Nature, and Mobility of Ions of Atmospheric Importance- G.A. Dawson & V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 454)
  - An Updated Review of the Literature on Gas-to-Aerosol Conversion- V.A. Mohnen & E.G. Walther, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 455)
  - Ternary System for the Atmospheric Aerosol Formation- C.S. Kiang, V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 456)
  - Precipitation Scavenging- R.G. Semonin & R.W. Beadle, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 457)
  - Precipitation Scavenging- R.G. Semonin & R.W. Beadle, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 458)
  - Time Dependent Behevior of Stored Precipitation Samples- J.A. Kadlecek & V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 463)
  - Testimony Presented to the Congress of the United States House of Reprentatives Committee on Science & Technology- V.A. Mohnen, 1975 August 7 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 467)
  - A Mechanism for Hydrochloric Acid Production in Cloud- G.K. Yue, V.A. Mohnen, and C.S. King, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 468)
  - Solar Energy Development & Implementation- R.Stewart & V.A. Mohnen, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 469)
  - Ozone Measurements in Rural Area- V.A. Mohnen & A.W. Hogan, 1977 December 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 470)
  - Measurements of Background Hyydrocarbons in Remote Areas- R.Whitby, L. Roland, V.A. Mohen, and P.Coffey, 1976 November (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 471)
  - Air Quality & Automobile Emission Control, 1974 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 472)
  - An Inexpensive Differential Thermal Analysis System for the teaching Laboratory- E.G. Malawer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 477)
  - Photochemically Indiced Free Radical Reactions in Nitrogen Dioxide- Acetaldehyde Mixtures- E.R. Allen, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 478)
  - Recommendations, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 479)
  - Properties & Reactions of Carbon Monoxide, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 480)
  - Sources, Occurrence, and Fate of Atmospehric Carbon Monoxide, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 481)
  - On the Formation of Langevin Ions in Water Supersaturated Air Jets- E.Barreto, 1968 May (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 483)
  - Electrostatics & Tanker Explosions- E. Barreto, 1971 April (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 484)
  - The Facts Concerning Static Electricity & Their Association with the Tanker Explosion Problem- E. Barreto, 1972 April (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 486)
  - The Possbility of Electrical Discharges in the Accident of the S.S. Pegasus- E.Barreto, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 487)
  - The Onset of Long Electrical Discharges in Clean Air- E.Barreto & H. Jurenka, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 488)
  - The Freshwater to Air Transfer of Microorganisms & Organic Matter- D.C. Blanchard & B.C Parker, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 500)
  - Nature's Microtome: Bursting Bubbles at the Surface of the Sea- D.C. Blanchard, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 501)
  - Discussions: Airborne Sea Salt Sedimentation Measurements & A Method of Reproducing Ambient Sedimentation Rates for the Study of its Effect on Vegetation- D.C. Blandchard, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 502)
  - The Influence of Dissolved Organic Material in the Sea on the Ejection Heights of Jet Drops- D.C. Blanchard, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 503)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1972 April 12 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 504)
  - Refrences &Unrefernces- D.C. Blanchard, 1974 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 505)
  - On the Truth Behind the Invention of the Leyden Jar- D.C. Blanchard, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 506)
  - Mass Spectrometer Studies of A- and B-piene- T.W. Norton, 1972-1973 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 507)
  - Summer Report 1968- T. Norton (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 510)
  - Solar Energyy Experiments for High School- T.W. Norton, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 511)
  - Mini- Project Final Report: Independent Study Program in Solar Energy- T.W. Norton, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 512)
  - Energy for the Future- T.W. Norton, 1977 January (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 513)
  - Energy: The Solar Prospect- D. Hayes, 1977 June (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 515)
  - ASRC Whiteface Observatory- R.E. Falconer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 516)
  - Book Reviews- R. Falconer, 1977 November (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 517)
  - Stream Valleys Can be Saved- A.E Lewis, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 518)
  - Weather Wise- R. Falconer, 1975 October 2 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 519)
  - Snowfall Properties of Lake Erie & Ontario Storms- J.E. Jiusto & M.L. Kaplan, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 521)
  - Lake Ontario Atlas: Chemsitry- E.R. Allen, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 526)
  - Lake Ontario Atlas: Climatetology, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 527)
  - Lake Ontario Atlas: Internal Waves, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 529)
  - Fotografic in de Muteorologic- M. Koldovoshy, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 550)
  - Reviews: Sonw Crystals- V.J. Schaefer, 1964 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 551)
  - Book Reviews: Probbing the Atmosphere- the Story of meterology- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 552)
  - Cloud Seeding- V.J. Schaefer, 1962 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 553)
  - Careers in the Expanding Industrial Field- V.J. Schaefer, 1962 July 2 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 554)
  - Things in the Air- V.J. Schaefer, 1967 November 1 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 555)
  - Snow - V.J. Schaefer, 1968 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 556)
  - Simple Equitment for Atmospheric Research- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 557)
  - After a quarter of a century- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 558)
  - The Formation of Ice Crystals Under Electrical Stress, 1969 September 18-24 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 559)
  - Needed- A Better Energy Sink- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 560)
  - New Field Evidence of Inadvertent Modification of the Atmosphere- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 562)
  - The Measurement of Aerosol Particles on a Global Scale- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 566)
  - Natural Sciences Institute Schoharie Region Program- V.J. Schaefer & A. Hulstrunk, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 567)
  - Cameras for Time-Lapse Photography- J. Aloway, C.B. Moore, and B. Vonnegut, 1970 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 569)
  - Charging of Droplets by Impulse Corona- C.T. Phelps & B. Vonnegut, 1970 August 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 570)
  - Estimated Possible Effecrs of AgI Cloud Seeding on Human Health- R.B. Standler & B. Vonnegut, 1972 December (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 571)
  - Electrical Breakdown Caused bu Dust Motion in Low Pressure Atmospheres: Consideration for Mars- H.F. Eden & B. Vonnegut, 1973 June (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 572)
  - Electrical Balance In the Lower Atmosphere- B. Vonnegut, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 573)
  - Cornona produced by Splashing of Water Drops on a Water Surface in a Strong Electric field- C.T. Phelps, R.F. Griffiths, and B. Vonnegut, 1973 February (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 574)
  - Direct Measurement of Vertical Potential Differences In the Lower Atmosphere- B. Vonnegut & R. Markson, 1973 July 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 575)
  - Ice Nuclection by Soild Solution of Silver- Copper Iodide - R.E. Passarelli Jr., H. Chessin, and B. Vonnegut, 1973 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 576)
  - Charge Transfer from a Highly Electrically Stressed Watr Surface during Drop Impact- R.F Griffiths, C.T. Phelps, and B. Vonnegut, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 577)
  - Electrical Potential Above Ocean Waves- B. Vonnegut, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 578)
  - Ice Nucelation by Miersite- R.E. Passarelli J.r, H.Chesin, and B. Vonnegut, 1974 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 579)
  - Instrument for measuring maximum thunderstorm Electric Field Intensity- B. Vonnegut and B.W. Rechintzer, 1974 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 580)
  - Ice Nucleation in a Supercold Cloud by CuI- 3AgI &AgI Aerosols-R.E. Passarelli Jr. H. Chasin, and B. Vonnegut, 1974 December (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 581)
  - Comment on ' The Electrification of The Thunderclouds & the Rain gush' - B. Vonnegut, 1975 January 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 582)
  - Comments on 'Electrification of Condensing & Evaporating Liquid Drops'- R.F. Griffiths & B. Vonnnegut, 1975 January (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 583)
  - Electrostatic Technique for Measuring Velocity of small projectiles in transit through glass Barrel- B. Vonnegut & D. Keller, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 584)
  - Possible Consequences of Global Dispersion of Krypton 85- W.L. Beck, D.T. Shaw, and B. Vonnegut, 1975 May (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 585)
  - Tape Recoeder Photocell Instrument for Dectecting & Recording Lightning Strokes- R.F. Griggiths & B. Vonnegut, 1975 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 586)
  - Investigation of the Pseudobinary Soild Solutions of AgI- CuI by means of X-Ray Diffraction- H. Chasin, R.E. Passarelli Jr., and B. Vonnegut, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 587)
  - Comment on ' The Relation of Electrical Activity to Tornadoes' by R.P. Davies- Jones and J.H. Golden- B. Vonnegut, 1975 November 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 588)
  - Detachment of Pendant Water Drops by High Voltage Pulses- M. Nifuka and B. Vonnegut, 1989 December (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 589)
  - Luminous Electrical Phenomina Associated with Nocturnal Tornadoes in Huntsville,Albama, 3 April 1974- O.H. Vaughan Jr. & B. Vonnegut, 1976 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 590)
  - Wind Speeds Required to Draw straw & splinters into wood - D. Killer,B. Vonnegut, 1976 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 591)
  - Wind Speed Estimation Based on the Penetration of Straws and Splinters Into Wood- D.Killer & B. Vonnegut, 1976 October (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 592)
  - Charged Drops Produced by Bursting of Bubbles at the Surface of Organic Liquids= M. Nifuku, B. Vonnegut, and D.C. Blandchard, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 593)
  - Solar Sector Weather Relationships- B. Vonnegut, 1974 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 594)
  - Increased Rates of Rainfall Production in Electricfield Clouds- P.R. Brazier-Smith, S.G. Jennings, and J. Latham, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 595)
  - Comment on ' A Quantitative Assessment of Precipitation Mechanisms of Thunderstorm Electrification- B. Vonnegut, 1972 June 28 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 596)
  - A Technique for Measuring Relative Threshold Nucleation Temperatures for Active Nucleation Catalysts- R.E. Passarelli Jr., H. Chasin, and B. Vonnegut, 1973 March (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 597)
  - Fields Charges Currents- B. Vonnegut, 1975 March (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 600)
  - Field Generation and Dissipation Currents in Thunderclouds as a Result of the Movement of Charged Hydroneteors- R.F. Griffiths & J. Lathem, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 601)
  - Comments on " The Mesurement of Charge & Size of Raindrops: Parts I and II" - R.F. Griffiths, 1975 April (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 602)
  - Use of Satellites in Studiying Bears- Status Report F.C. Craighead Jr., 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 604)
  - Electrical Corona from Melting Hailstoones- R.F. Griffiths, J. Lathem, and R.L. Reed, 1976 April (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 605)